change title nehru trophy to "Pulinkunnu Vallamkali (Rajiv Gandhi Trophy)"
its description is 
:The Rajiv Gandhi Trophy Boat Race, locally known as Pulinkunnu Vallamkali, is an annual snake boat race held on the last Saturday of August (or early September) at the Pampa River in Pulinkunnu, Alappuzha, Kerala. It commemorates late Prime Minister Rajiv Gandhi's 1985 visit to Kuttanad and features high-speed competition among Chundan Vallams (snake boats).
map link https://maps.app.goo.gl/JjwcFtEcYeiRcuKT8

